{
  "Olympics": [
    {
      "question": "Where were the first modern Olympics held?",
      "type": "radio",
      "options": {
        "1" : "London",
        "2" : "Paris",
        "3" : "Rome",
        "4" : "Athens"
      },
      "answer": "Athens"
    },
    {
      "question": "How many countries participated in the 1932 Winter Olympics? ",
      "type": "text",
      "answer": "17"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which color is one of the Olympic rings?",
      "type": "multi",
      "options": {
        "1" : "Blue",
        "2" : "Red",
        "3" : "Pink",
        "4" : "Black"
      },
      "answer": ["1", "2", "4"]
    },
    {
      "question": "How many countries participated in the 1932 Winter Olympics? ",
      "type": "text",
      "answer": "17"
    },
    {
      "question": "Where were the 2008 Olympic Summer Games held?",
      "type": "radio",
      "options": {
        "1" : "Beijing",
        "2" : "Seoul",
        "3" : "Tokyo",
        "4" : "Montreal"
      },
      "answer": "Beijing"
    },
    {
      "question": "What tragic event almost ruined the 1972 Olympics?",
      "type": "radio",
      "options": {
        "1" : "A plane crash",
        "2" : "A boating accident",
        "3" : "Athletes taken hostage",
        "4" : "A bus accident"
      },
      "answer": "Athletes taken hostage"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which country, as of 2010, has the most Olympic gold medals? ",
      "type": "radio",
      "options": {
        "1" : "USA",
        "2" : "China",
        "3" : "Great Britain",
        "4" : "Germany"
      },
      "answer": "USA"
    },
    {
      "question": "The very first record of the Olympics was in what year?",
      "type": "radio",
      "options": {
        "1" : "1558 BC",
        "2" : "1120",
        "3" : "440",
        "4" : "776 BC"
      },
      "answer": "776 BC"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which country has the most Olympic medals as of 2010?",
      "type": "radio",
      "options": {
        "1" : "Soviet Union",
        "2" : "Germany",
        "3" : "France",
        "4" : "USA"
      },
      "answer": "USA"
    },
    {
      "question": "The games were held as a tribute to which god?",
      "type": "radio",
      "options": {
        "1" : "Athena",
        "2" : "Mars",
        "3" : "Zeus",
        "4" : "Pluto"
      },
      "answer": "Zeus"
    },
    {
      "question": "Officially known as the Games of the X Olympiad, which American city hosted the 1932 Summer Olympics?",
      "type": "radio",
      "options": {
        "1" : "New York",
        "2" : "Atlanta",
        "3" : "Washington",
        "4" : "Los Angeles"
      },
      "answer": "Los Angeles"
    }
  ]
}
